powerhouselive.net 2019-06-18

# :: POWERHOUSE :: Live

Safeguarding your privacy and the security of your personal information isimportant to us. Please take a few minutes to read the following policy so thatyou understand how we treat your personal information. As we continuouslyimprove and expand our services, this policy might change without notice, soplease check it periodically. If you have questions about our privacy policy,please contact us via host@powerhoselive.net at your convenience.

▶  **Purpose**

Powerhouse has adopted this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of itspolicies with respect to information collected from the website. Your use ofthe Powerhouse website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy andyour consent to the practices it describes. 

▶  **PersonallyIdentifiable Information**

Personally, Identifiable Information is any information that concerns youindividually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name,address, telephone/fax number, email address any information you submit topowerhouselive.net that identifies you individually. The website will notcollect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provideit. Therefore, if you do not want us to obtain any personally identifiableinformation about you, please do not submit it to us. 

You can visit and browse powerhouselive.net without revealing personallyidentifiable information about yourself, but not all functions will beavailable to you. You would have to choose to disclose personally identifiableinformation about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. The WebSites and the Applications may collect personally identifiable informationabout you by methods such as the following:

_  
_**_Registration Forms_** **    ** 

If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion, to become aregistered user of powerhouselive.net to opt-in to receive Powerhouse’s concertinformation through various email applications, you must apply by filling outthe registration form available on powerhouselive.net. This form requirescertain personally identifiable information that may include, withoutlimitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, areasof interest, product usage, credit/debit card number(s) with associatedexpiration date(s), CVV and billing zip code(s), and/or a unique individualpassword.

_  
_**_Transactions and Activity_** **      **

If you become a registered user if you conduct transactions through thewebsite, we will collect information about the transactions you engage in whileon the Web Sites Application and your other activity on the website. Thisinformation may include, without limitation, areas of the website that youvisit, transaction type, content that you view, download submit, transactionamount, payment, and billing information as well as the nature, quantity andprice of the goods services you exchange and the individual sentities with whomyou communicate transact business.

_  
_**_Email and other voluntary communications_** **       **

You may also choose to communicate with us through email, by telephone, inwriting, through other means. We also collect the information in these communications,and such information may be personally identifiable.

▶  **Information Use**

Powerhouse may use the personally identifiable information collectedthrough its website primarily for such purposes as; 

·         helping toestablish and verify the identity of users

·         opening,maintaining, administering and servicing users' accounts memberships

·         processing,servicing, enforcing transactions and sending related communications

·         providing servicesand support to users

·            providing users with product service updates, promotional noticesand offers, and other information about

          Powerhouse concerts

·         responding to yourquestions inquiries, comments and instructions

·         protecting oursystems from fraud and unlawful access

·         maintaining thesecurity and integrity of its systems.

▶  **Disclosure ofInformation**

Powerhouse does not provide personally identifiable information tounaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you.Powerhouse may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate itsWeb Sites, payment processing, for other reasons related to the operation ofits business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiableinformation for that purpose. These companies may only use such personallyidentifiable information for the purpose performing those functions and may notuse it for any other purpose. Powerhouse may also disclose personallyidentifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, suchas in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request investigation, asotherwise permitted by law. 

▶  **Security**

Powerhouse maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards tohelp guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are beingoffered on the website, all pertaining data and information are transmittedfrom your computer to Powerhouse's server in encrypted form usingindustry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect suchinformation from interception. Powerhouse restricts any and all authorizedaccess to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimatepurpose to know that information to provide products services to you and thosepersons you have authorized to have access to such information. credit/debitcard number(s) you elect to provide on file as part of your online profile foruse when placing an order through Powerhouse website will be tokenized andmaintained in an encrypted format by a third-party provider to further lowerany risk. It is your responsibility to protect the integrity of your ownaccount by keeping your account name and password safe. Please be aware,however, that any email other transmission you send through the internet cannotbe completely protected against unauthorized interception. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect personally identifiable informationonline, we also take measures to protect your information off-line. All of ourusers' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need theinformation to perform a specific task are granted access to identifiableinformation. Furthermore, all employees are fully informed about our securityand privacy practices and updated as new policies are added revised.

▶  **Revision Date**

This policy waslast updated December 10, 2013.
